That
[music]
Welcome to Against the Clock Your
starcast can be like this 1200 I do
best places in the evening
What to do while watching four Where to do New York
What can those who have this stock do It may take
some time to get into print
In the front, you can manipulate the stock from 10 percent to
20 percent To
see, you see the stock share holding was long
General Insurance closing was around 1191
Now see the stock share holding The stock
holding of this hair oil filter is visible here It is showing around 48 percent
Fish that the addition is not
visible here It is showing 26 percent
Affected see it is decreasing in remedy
Despite this it keeps
showing Discarding has increased here
Now click on what you have written Show your 11
versions Public holding Here
this is the weekly chart of ICICI Lombard General Insurance on the moving chart
In the weekly chart, the price in the stock was
₹800 5 lakhs on 16 March 2019 Now
After putting five rupees a kilo, the stock kept
rising and Stark got hold of it. In
September 2001, it fell to 1675
or ₹100. It was
in Delhi that you had
made a subscription pass,
try to make it again by making a passport and from here
again
subscribed from the top and
in the line to be done,
11 it went out at around 1200. Raghava
below the pink line and approached 1201 below.
Take this stock, there
is a big negative thing here and on the top, it has been
tried most of the times, the operator has
stopped taking it out and
will try to come out from here, which will start as soon as it
starts, there can be a big fall from here,
hence you
can take a risk in Star with great caution.
Today, Stars are banned on the bill for the top,
when can those people keep their Star Plus pink line? Those who had made
this stock at Rs.12,
they too, their Star Plus is
around Rs.1200.  You can keep it invested because you can
also take the figure of 1200 and it was
acting as a very strong support for Rs.12 which has not come down till today. The
biggest negative thing here in this trial is that
if it closes again at the typing line and
starts moving upwards then this stock will be
in the past from here. Till then this topic
wise will keep testing by doing its prosperity. Till then there will be a
negative thing for the stock. Let's see
so that you will get the link from the bank.
You should make today's conditioner of this stock
along with the disappearance of the June 2012 scandal of
Rs. 1150. You can use this trick
with Shankar below the bill for Rs. 1150. If you
get it in any way for gas in China at around Rs. 1100.90 then you can use this
trick at Rs. 1180.90. Labels Abhishek Bachchan. The
target of starting juice has been crossed, go to the weekly chart and
see the recording of this chart, its
first target has been crossed, it is around Rs.
1100.  Twenty rupees are going out, 1100 Vansh Yaar
's juice has gone out, it is going up to about 1072, it has gone up by hitting the
target of ₹1000, it has gone out
almost ₹1000, it can go up to ₹1000
also or you
can subscribe here as per your wish,
while typing in the market, definitely put union, do
not work here, falling stock is
always amazing,
subscribe to the channel to get such interesting videos, the
message will be the voting line, if the
extra closing pin line is on Guru
and 12 is on it in the daily chart, then you should
immediately exit from the position as per your wish and remove it from your portfolio,
before taking stock limit of ICICI Lombard General Insurance stock, definitely consult your financial advisor,
thank you.